{
    "id": "37872b073b53425d91073352aa11958d",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The car sustained .................................................. damage in the accident.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heavy",
                "heavily",
                "heavier"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79b46d16071b4503999c1c87c93ac1fc"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................................. dog has his day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "All"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a631d95a60a14615968d3be46243a351"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a man of ......................................... words.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "574fb295ceea470bb4eed9e272733432"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... answer is quite right.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "244611c2cd704e23a62fa259eb9125d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The way was long, the wind was ..............................................., the minstrel was infirm and old.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cold",
                "colder",
                "coldly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cbaa5122655948728c8a4ede6fd279a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "John won ............................................. prize in the quiz competition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "first",
                "the first"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "305c34858e3949328a400997aaa51172"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy stood on the .................................... deck.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "burn",
                "burning",
                "burned"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1797915b594047ccb003265d05acf6c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "King Francis was a ......................................... king and loved a royal sport.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hearty",
                "heartily"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec18be9c95c14e3587200b4fd68d9dd4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a ....................................... fellow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "brave",
                "braver",
                "bravely"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d097f5e0e72a4c7d8cd0c760bdc10952"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the furrowed land stood the ..................................... oxen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "patient",
                "patience"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4f8bfa3663642f0ac63526f88a48d62"
        }
    ]
}